

CONTACT DETAILS

Chennai, Tamil Nadu

(+91) 9940413737

☐ 1 Oct '00

in LinkedIn

SKILLS

Networking

Security operation Centre

Penetration testing - website

Cloud Security - AWS

Penetration testing - Cloud

Digital Forensics

Linux

Windows

Frontend - HTML, CSS, JS

LANGUAGES

Tamil

Advanced

English

Intermediate

Hindi

Basic

Pravin S



OBJECTIVE

I am a Ethical hacker with robust problem-solving skills and proven experience in creating and testing and protect the **website**, **cloud AWS**, in a test-driven environment. and I have six months experience of real time. Delivering engaging and informative training sessions to diverse audiences, including IT professionals, employees of organizations, students, or anyone interested in learning about cybersecurity.

EDUCATION

Panimalar Engineering College, MECHANICAL- B.E

Jun 2017 - Apr 2018

Kalaimagal Vidyalaya Matric Higher Sec school - HSC

Apr 2018 — Jul 2022

Little Flowers Matric Hr Sec School- SSLC

Jun 2015 — Apr 2016

WORK EXPERIENCE

CyberFort DigiSec Solution Private Ltd, Chennai-Associate security consultant

Sep 2022 — Feb 2023

• I have some experience in Security Operation Centre of **L1** and **L2** role project, security consultant for **cloud** and I was maintained the **cloud security domain** and I worked in **VAPT** role for 2 months project **Cert-IN process** and great experience in **security consultant.**

CoNet Academy

Mar 2023 - Jun 2023

 Demonstrating practical applications of cybersecurity tools and techniques through hands-on labs and exercises to help participants gain practical skills.

CERTIFICATIONS

Certied Ethical Hacker

24 Mar 2022 EC - COUNCIL

AWS - shared responsibility model

2Dec 2022 AWS

Certified Cloud Security Engineer - CCSE

EC - COUNCIL PURSUING

Powered by: ilaforplacements.com